Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection, 63573
  - Composer: Kahnt, G. Title: Der Apotheker Uniform Title: Apotheker Publisher information: Bonn-Wiesbaden (Germany): Rud. Erdmann Plate Number: R. 880 E., undated; 31142040613401; 65663 (Box 156, Folder 2445)
  - Composer: Kalliwoda, Johann Wenzel [Kalivoda, Jan Krtitel Václav] Title: Liebe und Wein Uniform Title: Liebe und Wein (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 403, undated; 31142040613328; 65662 (Box 164, Folder 2770)
  - Composer: Kalman, E. Title: Die Csarasfuerstin Uniform Title: Csarasfuerstin, undated; 31142040613450; 65661 (Box 151, Folder 2206)
  - Composer: Kalman, Emmerich Title: Countess Maritza. Selection Uniform Title: Countess Maritza. Selection Publisher information: New York: Harms Incorporated Plate Number: 7730-10, undated; 31142040613377; 65660 (Box 159, Folder 2584)
  - Composer: Kalman, Emmerich Title: Countess Maritza. Selection Uniform Title: Grafin Mariza. Selection; arr. Publisher information: New York: Harms Inc., undated; 31142040614268; 65659 (Box 30, Folder 356)
  - Composer: Kalman, Emmerich Title: Gruss mir mein Wien Uniform Title: Grafin Mariza. Gruss mir mein Wien Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Octava, Music Co. Ltd. Plate Number: Oct. 3, undated; 31142040613518; 65658 (Box 145, Folder 1920)
  - Composer: Kalman, Emmerich Title: Kusslied aus der Operette Ein Herbstmanover Uniform Title: Herbstmanover. Kusslied Publisher information: New York: Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: K. and W. 350., undated; 31142040614268; 65657 (Box 30, Folder 358)
  - Composer: Kalman, Emmerich Title: Potpourri aus der Operette Die Csardasfurstin Uniform Title: Die Csardasfurstin. Potpourri; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Josef Weinberger Plate Number: J. W. 2018., undated; 31142040614268; 65656 (Box 30, Folder 357)
  - Composer: Kalman, Emmerich Title: Sari. Selection. Der Zigeunerprimas Uniform Title: Sari. Selection. Der Zigeunerprimas; arr. Publisher information: New York: Jos. W. Stern Plate Number: 7636, undated; 31142040614268; 65655 (Box 30, Folder 359)
  - Composer: Kammerlander, Carl Title: In Vino Juventus Uniform Title: In Vino Juventus Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 21245., undated; 31142040613328; 65654 (Box 164, Folder 2761)
  - Composer: Kampf, Karl Title: Jugend Uniform Title: Jugend, undated; 31142040613328; 65653 (Box 164, Folder 2755)
  - Composer: Kander, John Title: Cabaret Uniform Title: Cabaret. Cabaret Publisher information: New York: Sunbeam Music Corp., undated; 31142040613518; 65652 (Box 145, Folder 2033)
  - Composer: Karl, E., arr. Title: Des Deutschen Furcht Uniform Title: Deutschen Furcht Publisher information: Milwaukee: G. Reuther and Son Co. Music Printers, undated; 31142040613476; 65651 (Box 149, Folder 2153)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Die Hutte Uniform Title: Hutte Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Kahnt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4875, undated; 31142040613419; 65650 (Box 155, Folder 2406)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Komm' in die stille Nacht Uniform Title: Komm' in die stille Nacht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Richard Kaun (Paris and Co., Berlin [printer]) Plate Number: R. K. 1514, undated; 31142040613260; 65649 (Box 170, Folder 3024)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Maria Magdalena. Symphonischer Prolog Uniform Title: Maria Magdalena. Symphonischer Prolog Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Kahnt (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 3982b, undated; 31142040614268; 65648 (Box 30, Folder 360)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Requiem Uniform Title: Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 8189 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613278; 65647 (Box 169, Folder 2948)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Requiem Uniform Title: Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 8190 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613278; 65646 (Box 169, Folder 2949)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Requiem Uniform Title: Requiem Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.8193 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614250; 65645 (Box 31, Folder 361)
  - Composer: Kaun, Hugo Title: Vale carissima! Uniform Title: Vale carissima! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Kahnt Nachfolger (W. Benicke, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4585, undated; 31142040613245; 65644 (Box 172, Folder 3121)
  - Composer: Keiser, R. A. Title: Dinah from Carolina. Cake Walk Two-Step Uniform Title: Dinah from Carolina; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5574-17, undated; 31142040613088; 65643 (Box 123, Folder 1787)
  - Composer: Keiser, Robert A. Title: Fashions Caprice Uniform Title: Fashions Caprice Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 4-19-60436-4, undated; 31142040612874; 65642 (Box 102, Folder 1367)
  - Composer: Keldorfer, Victor Title: Die Trappisten Uniform Title: Trappisten Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Adolf Robitschek (Jos. Eberle and Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: A. R. 4150a., undated; 31142040613245; 65641 (Box 172, Folder 3135)
  - Composer: Keldorfer, Victor Title: Die Trappisten Uniform Title: Trappisten Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Adolf Robitschek (Jos. Eberle and Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: A.R.4149, undated; 31142040612866; 65640 (Box 101, Folder 1325)
  - Composer: Keldorjen, Viktor Title: Dorfschwalben aus Osterreich Uniform Title: Dorfschwalben aus Osterreich, undated; 31142040613120; 65639 (Box 127, Folder 1845)
  - Composer: Keler-Bela Title: French Comedy (Franzosische Lustspiel). Overture Uniform Title: French Comedy. Overture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10792-62, undated; 31142040614250; 65638 (Box 31, Folder 362)
  - Composer: Keler-Bela Title: The Son of the Puszta (Der Sohn der Heide) Uniform Title: Son of the Puszta; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10274-26, undated; 31142040614250; 65637 (Box 31, Folder 363)
  - Composer: Keler-Bela Title: Ungarische Lustspiel-Overture Uniform Title: Ungarische Lustspiel-Overture; arr. Publisher information: New York: J. Schott, undated; 31142040614250; 65636 (Box 31, Folder 364)
  - Composer: Keller, Georg Title: Liebesgestandniss Uniform Title: Liebesgestandniss Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5155 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612833; 65635 (Box 98, Folder 1241)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Die Amsel sang Uniform Title: Amsel sang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg Plate Number: 5119, undated; 65634 (Box 223, Folder 151)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Hans im Unmut Uniform Title: Hans im Unmut Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 2074 Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613435; 65633 (Box 153, Folder 2330)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Hans im Unmut Uniform Title: Hans im Unmut Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H.2073 Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613435; 65632 (Box 153, Folder 2329)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Im Bivouak Uniform Title: Im Bivouak Publisher information: Zurich (Switzerland): Phil. Fries Plate Number: 511 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613344; 65631 (Box 162, Folder 2707)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Lerche und Nachtigall Uniform Title: Lerche und Nachtigall Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 5120 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613310; 65630 (Box 165, Folder 2815)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Schmiedelied fur Manner-Chor Uniform Title: Schmiedelied fur Manner-Chor Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G.H.2024., undated; 31142040614250; 65629 (Box 31, Folder 366)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Schmiedelied Uniform Title: Schmiedelied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 1954 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613260; 65628 (Box 170, Folder 2991)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Schmiedelied Uniform Title: Schmiedelied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G.H.1953 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614250; 65627 (Box 31, Folder 365)
  - Composer: Kempter, Lothar Title: Waldstimmen Uniform Title: Waldstimmen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G. H. 2571., undated; 31142040613237; 65626 (Box 173, Folder 3181)
  - Composer: Kennedy, Jimmy, and Michael Carr Title: South of the Border (Down Mexico Way) Uniform Title: South of the Border Publisher information: New York: Shapiro, Bernstein and Co. Inc., undated; 31142040613369; 65625 (Box 160, Folder 2589)
  - Composer: Kennedy, Jimmy Title: The Mistletoe Kiss Uniform Title: Mistletoe Kiss Publisher information: New York: Campbell-Connelly, Inc., undated; 31142040613369; 65624 (Box 160, Folder 2594)
  - Composer: Kern, Jerome Title: (When Your Heart's on Fire) Smoke Gets in Your Eyes Uniform Title: Smoke Gets in Your Eyes; arr. Publisher information: New York: T. B. Harms Co., undated; 31142040613468; 65623 (Box 150, Folder 2185)
  - Composer: Kern, Jerome Title: (When Your Heart's on Fire) Smoke Gets in Your Eyes Uniform Title: Smoke Gets in Your Eyes Publisher information: New York: T. B. Harms Co. Plate Number: T.B.H.Co. 362-3, undated; 31142040613385; 65622 (Box 158, Folder 2531)
  - Composer: Kern, Jerome Title: All the Things You Are Uniform Title: Very Warm for May. All the Things You Are; arr. Publisher information: New York: T. B. Harms Co. Plate Number: C-1007-4, undated; 31142040613385; 65621 (Box 158, Folder 2535)
  - Composer: Kern, Jerome Title: Look for the Silver Lining Uniform Title: Look for the Silver Lining Publisher information: New York: T. B. Harms Co. Plate Number: 171-4, undated; 31142040613385; 65620 (Box 158, Folder 2539)
  - Composer: Kernochan, John Title: As I Ride By Uniform Title: As I Ride By; arr. Publisher information: New York: Galaxy Music Corporation Plate Number: G. M. 1525-7, undated; 31142040613450; 65619 (Box 151, Folder 2241)
  - Composer: Ketelbey, Albert W. Title: A Dream of Christmas Uniform Title: Dream of Christmas; arr. Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Bosworth and Co. (Bosworth and Co., Ltd. [printer]) Plate Number: B. and Co., Ltd.17167., undated; 31142040614250; 65618 (Box 31, Folder 367)
  - Composer: Ketelbey, Albert W. Title: In a Chinese Temple Garden Uniform Title: In a Chinese temple garden; arr. Publisher information: New York: Bosworth and Co., Ltd. Plate Number: B. and Co., Ltd.,17022, undated; 31142040614250; 65617 (Box 31, Folder 368)
  - Composer: Ketelbey, Albert W. Title: In a Monastery Garden Uniform Title: In a Monastery Garden Publisher information: New York: T. B. Harms and Frances, Day and Hunter, undated; 31142040614250; 65616 (Box 31, Folder 369)
  - Composer: Ketterer, Ella Title: L'Argentine. Fantaisie Mazurka Uniform Title: L'Argentine Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 126, undated; 31142040612908; 65615 (Box 105, Folder 1458)
  - Composer: Kienzl, Wilhelm Title: Abendlied Uniform Title: Abendlied Plate Number: 296., undated; 31142040613500; 65614 (Box 146, Folder 2063)
  - Composer: Kienzl, Wilhelm Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Uniform Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 6288 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613336; 65613 (Box 163, Folder 2722)
  - Composer: Kienzl, Wilhelm Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Uniform Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 6289 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613336; 65612 (Box 163, Folder 2723)
  - Composer: Kienzl, Wilhelm Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Uniform Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 6290 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613336; 65611 (Box 163, Folder 2724)
  - Composer: Kienzl, Wilhelm Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Uniform Title: Kreuzritters Heimkunft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 6312 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613336; 65610 (Box 163, Folder 2725)
  - Composer: Kienzl, Wilhelm Title: Spinnerlied Uniform Title: Spinnerlied Plate Number: 298., undated; 31142040613500; 65609 (Box 146, Folder 2064)
  - Composer: King, Robert A. Title: Beyond the Gates of Paradise Uniform Title: Beyond the Gates of Paradise Publisher information: New York: Fesit and Frankenthaler, undated; 31142040612874; 65608 (Box 102, Folder 1362)
  - Composer: Kinkel, Johanna Title: Soldier's Farewell Uniform Title: Soldier's Farewell Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson and Co., undated; 31142040613260; 65607 (Box 170, Folder 3017)
  - Composer: Kinkel, Johannas Title: Ritters Abschied Uniform Title: Ritters Abschied Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth and Co., undated; 31142040613120; 65606 (Box 127, Folder 1838)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der Quacksalber oder Doctor Sagebein und sein Famulus Uniform Title: Quacksalber Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]), undated; 31142040613096; 65605 (Box 124, Folder 1796)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der Quacksalber oder Doctor Sagebein und sein Famulus Uniform Title: Quacksalber Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 3226, undated; 31142040613096; 65604 (Box 124, Folder 1794)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der Quacksalber oder Doctor Sagebein und sein Famulus Uniform Title: Quacksalber Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 3228, undated; 31142040613096; 65603 (Box 124, Folder 1795)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der Todte Schneider Uniform Title: Todte Schneider Plate Number: M.S. 351., undated; 31142040613021; 65602 (Box 117, Folder 1669)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der todte Schneider Uniform Title: Todte Schneider Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): M. Schloss, undated; 31142040613021; 65601 (Box 117, Folder 1670)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Die Gerichtssitzung Uniform Title: Gerichtssitzung Plate Number: M.S.225., undated; 31142040613062; 65600 (Box 121, Folder 1737)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Die Gerichtssitzung Uniform Title: Gerichtssitzung Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ries and Erler Plate Number: R. 5007 E., undated; 31142040613062; 65599 (Box 121, Folder 1736)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Fidelia. Quodlibet Oper in 2 Acten Uniform Title: Fidelia Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): M. Schloss (W. Clouth, Cologne [printer]) Plate Number: M.S.626, undated; 31142040613104; 65598 (Box 125, Folder 1808)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Kellner und Lord Uniform Title: Kellner und Lord Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4776, undated; 31142040613088; 65597 (Box 123, Folder 1766)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Das schonste Lied Uniform Title: Schonste Lied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 8109, undated; 31142040613492; 65596 (Box 147, Folder 2080)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Elfenlocken im Wald Uniform Title: Elfenlocken im Wald Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bosworth and Co. (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: B. and Co. 7102, undated; 31142040613427; 65595 (Box 154, Folder 2392)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Elslein mach' auf Uniform Title: Elsein mach' auf Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4534, undated; 31142040613393; 65594 (Box 157, Folder 2488)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Uniform Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Adolf Robitschek Plate Number: A. R. 1356a., undated; 31142040613393; 65593 (Box 157, Folder 2479)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Uniform Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Robay and Robitschek (Jos. Eberle and Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: R. and R. 1356., undated; 31142040613393; 65592 (Box 157, Folder 2478)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Es war einst eine schone Zeit Uniform Title: Es was einst eine schone Zeit Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 8305-3, undated; 31142040613369; 65591 (Box 160, Folder 2609)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Frau Wirtin, schenkt ein! Uniform Title: Frau Wirtin, schenkt ein! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4657 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613351; 65590 (Box 161, Folder 2639)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Im Abendwinde Uniform Title: Im Abendwinde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4306 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613328; 65589 (Box 164, Folder 2763)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Orakel Uniform Title: Orakel Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4568 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613294; 65588 (Box 167, Folder 2895)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Stillleben Uniform Title: Stillleben Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bosworth and Co. Plate Number: B. and Co. 7099, undated; 31142040613252; 65587 (Box 171, Folder 3051)
  - Composer: Kistler, Cyrill Title: Kunihild. Overture Uniform Title: Kunihild. Overture, Act 3 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon Plate Number: C.S.2049 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614243; 65586 (Box 32, Folder 383)
  - Composer: Kistler, Cyrill Title: Kunihild. Overture Uniform Title: Kunihild. Overture, Act 3 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon Plate Number: C.S.2050 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614243; 65585 (Box 32, Folder 384)
  - Composer: Kistler, Cyrill Title: Kunihild. Prelude Uniform Title: Kunihild. Overture, Act 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 19864-20, undated; 31142040614243; 65584 (Box 32, Folder 385)
  - Composer: Klanert, Karl Title: Von dir zu scheiden Uniform Title: Von dir zu scheiden Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6462 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613443; 65583 (Box 152, Folder 2288)
  - Composer: Klanert, Karl Title: Vor dir zu scheiden Uniform Title: Vor dir zu scheiden Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6462 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612866; 65582 (Box 101, Folder 1323)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Das Ringlein Sprang Entzwei Uniform Title: Ringlein Sprang Entzwei Publisher information: Philadelphia: J. W. Jost Plate Number: 552, undated; 31142040613468; 65581 (Box 150, Folder 2173)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Das stille Thal Uniform Title: Stille Thal Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 21006-3, undated; 31142040613500; 65580 (Box 146, Folder 2073)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Fruhlings Erwachen Uniform Title: Fruhlings Erwachen Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 21005-15, undated; 31142040613393; 65579 (Box 157, Folder 2486)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Serenade Uniform Title: Serenade Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 14580-2 1/2, undated; 31142040613260; 65578 (Box 170, Folder 3006)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Vereins- und Willkomm' Gruss Uniform Title: Vereins- und Willkomm' Gruss, undated; 31142040613401; 65577 (Box 156, Folder 2447)
  - Composer: Kleffel, Arno Title: On Guard Uniform Title: Auf der Wacht; arr. Publisher information: New York: F. A. Rockar Plate Number: F. A. R. 770-2, undated; 31142040613450; 65576 (Box 151, Folder 2250)
  - Composer: Klein, Bruno Oscar Title: Le Secret d'Amour Uniform Title: Secret d'Amour Publisher information: New York: J. Fischer and Bro. Plate Number: J.F. and B. 3687-4, undated; 31142040612965; 65575 (Box 111, Folder 1596)
  - Composer: Klein, Bruno Oscar Title: No Stars in Heaven Uniform Title: Himmel hat keine Sterne Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 4-66-62739-5, undated; 31142040613401; 65574 (Box 156, Folder 2463)
  - Composer: Klein, Bruno Oscar Title: Soldier's March Uniform Title: Soldaten-Marsch Publisher information: New York ( of Amreica): Edward Schuberth and Co. Plate Number: C.F.T.131, undated; 31142040612890; 65573 (Box 104, Folder 1425)
  - Composer: Kleinfelder, R. Title: Hebe mich auf weichen Schwingen Uniform Title: Hebe mich auf weichen Schwingen Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth and Co. Plate Number: E.S. and Co. 3095, undated; 31142040613351; 65572 (Box 161, Folder 2650)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Abendruh Uniform Title: Abendruh Publisher information: New York Engraver: Otto Lobner, undated; 31142040613476; 65571 (Box 149, Folder 2137)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Bohmisches Volkslied Uniform Title: Bohmisches Volkslied Publisher information: New York Engraver: Otto Lobner, undated; 31142040613468; 65570 (Box 150, Folder 2177)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Frohliche Armuth Uniform Title: Frohliche Armuth Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6645-5, undated, undated; 31142040613369; 65569 (Box 160, Folder 2626)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Und botet ihr ein Bisthum mir Uniform Title: Und botet ihr ein Bisthum mir Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5570, undated; 31142040613237; 65568 (Box 173, Folder 3155)
  - Composer: Kling, Henri Title: The two little Bulfinches Uniform Title: Two little Bulfinches; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 11809-8 1/2, undated; 31142040614250; 65567 (Box 31, Folder 371)
  - Composer: Kling, Henri Title: The two little Bulfinches Uniform Title: Two little Bulfinches; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 11811-19, undated; 31142040614250; 65566 (Box 31, Folder 370)
  - Composer: Klinger, Achilles, arr. Title: Du, du liegst mir im Herzen Uniform Title: Du, du liegst mir im Herzen Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Richard Kaun Plate Number: R.K.802, undated; 31142040613500; 65565 (Box 146, Folder 2072)
  - Composer: Klugescheid, R., arr. Title: Paraphrase uber Mendelssohn's Es ist bestimmt Uniform Title: Paraphrase uber Mendelssohn's Es ist bestimmt, undated; 31142040612726; 65564 (Box 87, Folder 1098)